One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Inherited will...
the tides of time, and humanity's dreams...
They cannot be stopped.
As long as people seek freedom,
these things will never cease to be.
I only believe in the future -- I don't care if anyone laughs
That racing passion makes you shine
It's too bright, but I want to gaze at it
I sense "aesthetics" somewhere
I follow, follow in the footsteps
of a dream that resembles no one
Until I dramatically get it
I'm going to catch, catch the shape
of a dream no one can see
I'm going to go with you, so passionate feelings
I don't really need everything to add up
Rather than run-of-the-mill daily life,
run for paradise instead
Marine Branch 153
Shells Town, East Blue
"Cabin Boy"
Hey! Quit slackin' off!
Okay.
Hey, cabin boys!
After sweeping, wash the windows!
Yes, sir!
– One! Two! Three! Four!
The Trials of Koby-Meppo
I can't stand this. Forget Koby—
why do I have to be a cabin boy?!
Dammit! I only ended up here
because of that Straw Hat!
It's all his fault!
It's all because of Straw Hat
that I'm stuck doing this crap!
Helmeppo.
What do you want?!
Don't act like we're friends!
Nothing good comes from blaming Luffy
for everything that happens.
For a long time, you lived protected
by your father's influence.
But from now on, we need to
face forward and seek our own dreams!
What are you...?
I have a dream.
Someday, I will be a Marine officer
who cracks down on bad guys!
What are you going on about?!
A wimp like you becoming
an officer for the Marines?!
Quit dreaming!
I will do it!
I decided on it after seeing
how Luffy lives his life!
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!
This is what I've decided,
so if I die, then fine by me!
So just like Luffy, I've made up
my mind to risk everything
and pursue a goal of my own!
You see? So let's work hard together!
Screw you!
How dare you lecture me?!
Just when did you get
so full of yourself?!
What could you possibly learn
from that despicable Straw Hat?!
Don't insult Luffy!
I haven't said anything wrong!
Wrong or not,
you still piss me off!
Helmeppo! Please!
You have to be realistic.
Look who's talking!
Take this!
Get ahold of yourself!
Huh? What's going on?!
– W-We're sorry!
– We're sorry!
Really? The explosion earlier
was because of you?
So then they kicked
you out of the Marines?
Thank you.
No, we managed
to avoid being discharged.
But now we're under
a fifty-year contract with no pay.
Getting canned
would've been a mercy.
Attention!
I will now fill you in
on our current mission!
– Hey!
– What do you want?!
D-Daddy...
Morgan, a former Marine captain,
is to be sent to headquarters
to face a court-martial for the crimes
of military exploitation and civilian torment!
Today's mission is his transfer
and delivery to Vice Admiral Garp!
I am Captain "Axe-Hand" Morgan
of the Marines!
Scum without rank or status
should kneel before me!
This was the only outcome, wasn't it?
I'm not denying that he should be
court-martialed or whatever.
He deserves what's coming
to him, after all.
But even so, I used to respect him.
Damn it!
Why?!
Tell me, do you think
they'll execute him?
Th-That's...
There's probably no getting
around that either, huh?
That's just how Daddy is.
Helmeppo...
All hands on deck!
Fall in!
– It's Vice Admiral Garp!
– It's Garp the Fist!
So that's Marine Headquarters'
Vice Admiral Garp the Fist!
Vice Admiral Garp
Marine Headquarters
Traveling all over the Grand Line,
he's the hero of the seas!
Vice Admiral Garp, thank you
for personally coming all this way!
"Justice"
We hereby deliver to you Morgan!
Stop, Helmeppo!
Umm... Vice Admiral Garp?
Vice Admiral Garp!
Quiet!
I hear you.
I've been up for five days now.
Thank you for your hard work, sir!
It's no big deal since I'm trying for
a new doughnut-eating record.
Sir?
But a lack of rest and sleep
is getting to me after the 842nd one.
Old man, cut the sleeping act.
Everybody freeze!
Move and I'll hack up this cabin boy
and feed him to the sharks!
D-Daddy!
Please stop!
Helmeppo's your own son, isn't he?!
Son?! I don't need such a thing!
What I want is freedom!
I'll smash him to
a bloody pulp if need be!
D-Daddy...
H-Help me!
So long, suckers!
Helmeppo!
Ready the cannon!
Load! Aim!
Target: 16 degrees starboard.
Distance: eight, two,
six, three. Ready!
P-P-Please wait!
That's dangerous!
– What are you doing?!
– Get down from there!
P-Please don't shoot! My friend...
My friend's onboard!
Move.
No!
Then I'll cut you down!
That's much better than
just abandoning my friend!
Please! I'll go capture him myself!
Come back, you idiot!
There's no way you can capture him!
Just let him go.
He's either a complete lunatic, or...
What do we do?!
What's with all the racket?
I'm finally awake.
Vice Admiral Garp,
we thought you were a goner!
Huh?! Who's a goner?!
I missed it because I was asleep!
Where's the victim?!
Me?
I'm free!
Just you watch! The world
will kneel before me once again!
Today, I begin a new life
as the ruler of the Morgan Kingdom!
Now! Set our course west!
What are you doing?!
I said to set course due west!
No!
I'll have no part in this!
Despite what happened,
he still covered for us!
Even when getting sacked
by the Marines would end his dream!
After all that, he's still
protecting me! I can do it, too!
I'm going to capture you, Dad!
Just give up–
Are you dim?! Who do you think
you're talking to, huh?!
What can useless scum
like you do to me?!
Dammit!
Know your place, you pathetic insect!
As if I'd ever listen to you!
I'm the one who decides how I'll live!
Quit getting the wrong idea!
What can a piece of scum like you do?!
He isn't alone!
You!
Morgan!
Pathetic! Pathetic! Pathetic!
So what if a couple of insects
are swarming together?!
Get in my way, and I'll
end you both in one fell swoop!
I'm sorry you got dragged into this
when you tried to save me.
What are you talking about?
Aren't we friends?
Koby...
You damn insects
aren't even worth killing.
Never show yourselves to me again!
Morgan!
I'll let you go for today,
but someday I will surpass you!
Someday, I will catch you!
Just you wait!
Please forgive my poor supervision!
Letting him flee is
the biggest blunder in my life!
We're very sorry, sir!
These two are now forever
barred from military service!
You two truly are lost causes.
I doubt anyone anywhere
would take you in now.
And if we turn you loose,
you'd be a nuisance to all.
You leave me no choice.
Come with me to Marine Headquarters!
Vice Admiral! You're taking them
with you to Marine Headquarters?!
Am I not allowed?
No, do as you please.
Any objections, you two?
If you want to run away,
now's your chance.
Though I have no intention
of letting you say no.
My, oh my, what an odd day
this has been!
What?! Marine Headquarters?!
Yeah. Vice Admiral Garp seems
to be as eccentric as people say.
But doesn't he have
an exceptional reputation?
Yeah, you have no idea.
Then those two must show
a lot of promise.
Hm?
Stupid! Stupid! Stupid! Stupid! Stupid!
Why did you let them go
without saying anything?!
Stupid! Stupid!
Stupid! Stupid! Stupid!
I... wanted to play with them more.
I wanted to talk to them more.
I was learning how to cook so I could
make them tasty lunch boxes!
I didn't even get to say goodbye!
Ah... Um...
Why did they leave?!
Ah, I'm sorry! Forgive me!
Rika, that's enough. Leave him alone.
Don't worry. They'll surely be back...
once they become fine officers.
"The Marines"
But at any rate,
Marine Headquarters
can we really become Marines
by doing things like this?
This might be that
old dog's hobby, you know.
Hobby?
Yup. It's called "the retired geezer's
torment of youths."
Don't you think he's shifty
and strange enough for that?
Shut up, birds!